{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Pool Deck Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/62411/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62411,"taskName":"Pool Deck - Build","taskDescription":"Build a Pool Deck","xmTaskDescriptor":"Pool Deck Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"swimming pool, pool deck, pool decking","textMessagingName":"Build Pool Deck","rolloverLongDesc":"Build a New or Replace Existing Swimming Pool Deck","rolloverShortDesc":"Build a New or Replace Existing Pool Deck","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build a Swimming Pool Deck.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Pool Deck Building \u0026 Replacement \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Pool Deck Contractors","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":61,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Pool Deck Construction","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Pool Deck - Build","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Pool Deck Project","urlName":"Pool-Deck-Construction","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Pool Deck Builders in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Installation \u0026 Replacement","searchKeywords":"swimming,pool,swim,inground,above ground,pool deck, deck, decking","emcCategoryOid":-12070,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":8919,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62411/":{"taskOID":62411,"originalTaskOID":62411,"setID":8919,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6268,"questionDisplayText":"Deck Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What material do you want to build the deck with?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":203995,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stamped concrete","answerDisplayText":"Stamped concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1487,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Colored concrete","answerDisplayText":"Colored concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4867,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Interlocking  concrete pavers","answerDisplayText":"Pre-formed interlocking concrete pavers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2302,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Exposed aggregate (pebbles)","answerDisplayText":"Exposed aggregate (pebbles)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6354,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7582,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of pool will be remodeled?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11531,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11532,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7583,"questionDisplayText":"Pool Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What primary material is the pool surface made of?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11533,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11534,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11535,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6268,"questionDisplayText":"Deck Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What material do you want to build the deck with?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":203995,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stamped concrete","answerDisplayText":"Stamped concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1487,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Colored concrete","answerDisplayText":"Colored concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4867,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Interlocking  concrete pavers","answerDisplayText":"Pre-formed interlocking concrete pavers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2302,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Exposed aggregate (pebbles)","answerDisplayText":"Exposed aggregate (pebbles)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6354,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":203995,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stamped concrete","answerDisplayText":"Stamped concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1487,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Colored concrete","answerDisplayText":"Colored concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4867,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Interlocking  concrete pavers","answerDisplayText":"Pre-formed interlocking concrete pavers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2302,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Exposed aggregate (pebbles)","answerDisplayText":"Exposed aggregate (pebbles)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6354,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7582,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of pool will be remodeled?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11531,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11532,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11531,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11532,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7583,"questionDisplayText":"Pool Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What primary material is the pool surface made of?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11533,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11534,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11535,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11533,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11534,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11535,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}